allaboutcircuits.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which EETech Media collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://www.allaboutcircuits.com website ("Site").

### Personal identification information

As the Data Controller for our Users’ data, we may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. The collected information is not used for any additional purposes, such as to profile those who access our website. We do not make automated decisions based on the data any User provides.

Users may visit our Site anonymously. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. We use Facebook Pixel, Linkedin Pixel, and Google Analytics to gather and re-target to our audience.

### How we use collected information

EETech Media may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To run and operate our Site_  
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly. 
  * _To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * _To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * _To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 
  * _To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 

### Your Data Rights

Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) policies with which we comply, EU Users have eight data rights as follows:

  * **The right to be informed** : We will be transparent about how we use your data.
  * **The right of access** : Users will know exactly how we process their data, as well as what data about them is currently being stored.
  * **The right of rectification** : Users can have data rectified if it is incorrect or incomplete.
  * **The right to erasure** : Users may have their data deleted if they so choose. This is also known as the “right to be forgotten.”
  * **The right to restrict processing** : Users may restrict or completely block the processing of their personal data.
  * **The right to data portability** : Users may reuse their personal data for individual use.
  * **The right to object** : In some instances, Users may object to the use of their personal data.
  * **The rights of automated decision making and profiling** : Users may object to their use of their data as it relates to automatic processing without human intervention and consequences that have legal bearing on the User.

### Your Choices

**Access, Correction, Deletion.**  
We respect your privacy rights and provide you with reasonable access to the personal data that you may have provided through your use of the Site. If you wish to access or amend any personal data we hold about you, or to request that we delete any information about you, you may contact us as set forth in the “Contacting Us” section. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our database.

You may decline to share certain personal data with us, or choose to request the restriction or suppression of your personal data, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of the Site.

At any time, you may object to the processing of your personal data, on legitimate grounds, except if otherwise permitted by applicable law.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have not opted-out of these services.

### Law Enforcement and Legal Process

We may report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. We may also report any activities that we believe may aid a law enforcement investigation into unlawful activity. We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary, in our sole judgement, to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect the rights, property or safety, of the Site, the public, or another user. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Sharing Your Information as Permitted By Law

We may share your information with others as required by law. We may also share your information with others as permitted by law. This may include sharing your information with government entities or third-parties in response to subpoenas, court orders, other legal process. We may also share your information if we believe it is necessary to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims that have been brought against us, or to defend against possible legal claims that we determine might be brought against us.

### Electronic newsletters

If a user has opted-in, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, advertisements, etc. The User gives explicit consent to receive the Site’s newsletters by filling out the Site’s registration form, which includes registration for AllAboutCircuits.com, its forum, and newsletters, as clearly stated on the registration page. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email. We may share your contact information with our advertisers if you have shown an interest in their products/services (by clicking on their advertisement in our newsletters and consenting to receive their updates).

### Giveaways, Design Contests, Webinars & Industry White Papers

By registering and checking the opt-in checkbox for a Giveaway, Design Contest, Webinar or an Industry white paper, the User acknowledges that their contact information will be shared with the sponsoring company, as stated on the respective registration page.

### Registration Page Info Checkboxes

On our registration page, we partner with companies and provide an option to learn more about the company ("Example: Check the box to the left if you would like information about Company X"). If you check this checkbox, we will share your contact information with the sponsoring company.

### Surveys

Occasionally, we conduct user surveys to better understand the needs of our audience in order to improve our features. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any survey information about specific individuals with any third party without the user’s consent. By filling out surveys on our media properties, or social networks (e.g., Facebook), the user acknowledges that their contact information may be shared with companies that they mark having an interest in and consent receiving communication from.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### International transfer of data

If you are visiting this Site from outside the United States, please note that any personal data you agree to submit will be transferred to and housed in our U.S. servers. That data may then be transferred within the United States or transferred to other countries outside of the United States, where stringent data protection laws may not be in place. However, our collection, storage, and use of this data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.

Any data transferred from the EEA to the United States through our Site is compliant with the EU-US Privacy Shield. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

EETech Media has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact our Data Protection Officer. They can be reached by email at privacy@eetech.com or at the following address:

EETech Media, LLC  
ATTN: Data Protection Officer  
404 S. 8th St., Ste. 203  
Boise, ID 83702

This document was last updated on May 24, 2018
